BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Correspondence, 1944-1977; 1
  - General, 1944-1977; 1
    - Personal (3 of 4), 1948-1949 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Personal (4 of 4), 1948-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Personal (1 of 2), 1949 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Personal (2 of 2), 1949 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Personal Matters, 1970-1974 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Ph, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Ph, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Ph, 1954-1955 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Ph, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Ph, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Ph, 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Ph, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Ph, 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Pi, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Pi, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Pi-n, 1954-1955 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Pi-n, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Pi-n, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Pi-n, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Pi-n, 1958-1959 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Pi-n, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Po, 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Po, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Po, 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Po, 1955-1956 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Po, 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Po, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Po, 1958-1959 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Po, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Pr, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Pr, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Election, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Pr-z, 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Pr-z, 1955-1956 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Pr-z, 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Pr-z, 1957-1958 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Pr-z, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Pr-z, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Q, 1950-1951 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Q, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Q, 1955-1956 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Q, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Q, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Q, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Q, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Q, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Q, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Q, 1966-1970 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - R, 1946-1948 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - R, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - R, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - R (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - R (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - R, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - R (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - R (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - R, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - R, 1964-1966 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - R, 1966-1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - R, 1971-1975 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Ra, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Ra, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Ra-d, 1954-1955 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Ra-d, 1955-1956 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Ra-d, 1956-1957 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Ra-d, 1957-1958 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Ra-d, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Ra-d, 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Re, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Re, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations (1 of 2), 1948-1950 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Recommendations (2 of 2), 1948-1950 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Re-h, 1954-1955 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Re-h, 1955-1956 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Re-h, 1956-1957 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Re-h, 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Re-h, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Re-h, 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Ri, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Ri, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Ri-n, 1954-1955 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Ri-n, 1955-1956 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Ri-n, 1956-1957 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Ri-n, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Ri-n, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Ri-n, 1956, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Ro, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Ro, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Ro, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Ro, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Ro-t, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Ro-t, 1955-1956 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Ro-t, 1956-1957 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Ro-t, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Ru, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Ru, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Ru-z, 1954-1955 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Ru-z, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Ru-z (1 of 2), 1955-1959 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Ru-z (2 of 2), 1955-1959 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Ru-z, 1956-1957 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Ru-z, 1959-1960 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - S, 1945-1948 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - S, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - S (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - S (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - S, 1960-1964 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - S (1 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - S (2 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - S (3 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - S (4 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - S, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - S (1 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - S (2 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - S (3 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - S (1 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - S (2 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - S, 1966-1970 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - S, 1971-1975 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Sa, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Sa, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Sa, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Sa, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Sa, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Sa-b, 1954-1955 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Sa-b, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Sc, 1952 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Sc, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Sc, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Sc, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Sc, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Sc, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Sc-d, 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Sc-d, 1955-1956 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Se, 1952 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Se, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Se, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Se, 1957-1958 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Se, 1958-1959 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Se, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Se-g, 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Se-g, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Sh, 1952 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Sh, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Sh, 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Sh, 1955-1956 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Sh, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Sh, 1957-1958 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Sh, 1958-1959 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Sh, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Si, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Si, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Si, 1954-1955 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Si, 1955-1956 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Si, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Si, 1957-1958 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Si, 1958-1959 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Si, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Sk, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Sk, 1958-1959 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Sk, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Sk-e, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Sk-l, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Sk-l, 1954-1955 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Sk-l, 1955-1956 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Sm-n, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Sm-n, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Sm-n, 1954-1955 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Sm-n, 1955-1956 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Sm-n, 1956-1957 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Sm-n, 1957-1958 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Sm-n, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Sm-n, 1959-1960 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - So, 1951-1952 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - So, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - So, 1954-1955 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - So, 1955-1956 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - So, 1956-1957 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - So, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - So, 1959-1960 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Sp, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Sp, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Sp, 1956-1957 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Sp, 1957-1958 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Sp, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Sp, 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Sp-s, 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Sp-s, 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - St-u, 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - St-w, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - St-w, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - St-w, 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - St-w (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - St-w (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - St-w, 1956-1959 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - St-w, 1956-1957 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - St-w, 1957-1958 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - T, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - T (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - T (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - T, 1961-1963 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - T, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - T, 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - T, 1964-1966 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - T, 1966-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - T, 1971-1975 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Ta, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Ta, 1953 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Ta, 1956-1959 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Ta, 1959-1960 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Ta-d, 1954-1955 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Ta-d, 1955-1956 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Ta-d, 1956-1957 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Ta-d, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Te, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Te, 1953 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Te, 1958-1959 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Te, 1959 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Te-g, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Te-g, 1955-1956, 1935 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Te-g, 1956-1957 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Te-g, 1957-1958 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Telegrams In, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Telegrams Out, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Telegrams In, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Telegrams Out, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Telegrams Received During Illness, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Telegrams In, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Telegrams Out, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Telegrams In, 1954-1955 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams Out, 1954-1955 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Telegrams Out, 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Telegrams In, 1956-1957 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Telegrams Out, 1956-1957 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Telegrams In, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Telegrams Out, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Telegrams In, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Telegrams Out, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Telegrams In, 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Telegrams Out, 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Telegrams, 1961-1963 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Th, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Th, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Th-n, 1954-1955 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Th-n, 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Th-n, 1956-1957 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Th-n, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Th-n, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Th-n, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Thank You Letter for Russian Trip-Dr. and Mrs. W.R. White, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Thank You Letter-W.R. White, 1957 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - To, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - To, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - To, 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - To, 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - To, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - To, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - To-q, 1954-1955 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - To-q, 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Tr-z, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Tr-z, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Tr-z, 1954-1955 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Tr-z, 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Tr-z, 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Tr-z, 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Tr-z, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Tr-z, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - U, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - U, 1951-1952 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - U, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - U, 1954-1955 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - U, 1955-1956 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - U, 1956-1957 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - U, 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - U, 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - U, 1957, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - U, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - U, 1961-1962 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - U, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - U, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Unanswered Correspondence, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - V, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - V, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - V, 1952 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - V, 1953 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - V, 1954-1955 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - V, 1955-1956 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - V, 1956-1957 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - V, 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - V, 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - V, 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - V, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - V, 1961-1963 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - V, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - V, 1964-1965 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - V, 1966-1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Various Correspondence, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - W, 1945-1947 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - W, 1948 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - W, 1950 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - W (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - W (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - W, 1959-1961 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - W, 1960-1961 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - W (1 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - W (2 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - W (3 of 3), 1961-1963 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - W (1 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - W (2 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - W, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - W, 1966-1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - W, 1971-1975 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Wa, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Wa, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Wa-d, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Wa-d, 1955-1956 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Wa-d, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Wa-d, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Wa-d, 1958-1959 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Wa-d, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - We, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - We, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Wedding Announcements, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - We-g, 1954-1955 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - We-g, 1955-1956 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - We-g, 1956-1957 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - We-g, 1957-1958 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - We-g, 1958-1959 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - We-g, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Wh, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Wh, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Wh, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Wh, 1955-1956 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Wh, 1956-1957 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Wh, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Wh, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Wh-m, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - White-Business, 1948-1949 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - White-Correspondence, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - White-Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - White-Correspondence (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - White-Correspondence, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - White-Letters of Congratulation (1 of 2), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - White-Letters of Congratulation (2 of 2), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - White-Miscellaneous Personal, 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - White-Personal (1 of 3), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - White-Personal (2 of 3), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - White-Personal (3 of 3), 1948 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - White-Personal, 1950-1952 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - White-Personal, 1954-1955 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - White-Personal (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - White-Personal (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - White-Personal (1 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - White-Personal (2 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - White-Personal (3 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - White (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - White (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - White, 1960-1963 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - White (1 of 2), 1962-1975 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - White (2 of 2), 1962-1975 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - White Becomes President 1, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - White Becomes President 2, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - White Becomes President 3, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - White Becomes President 4, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - White Becomes President 5, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - White Becomes President 6, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - White Becomes President 7, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - White Becomes President 8, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - White Becomes President 9, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - White Becomes President 10, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - White Becomes President 11, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - White Becomes President 12, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - White Becomes President 13, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - White Becomes President 14, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - White Becomes President 15, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - White Becomes President 16, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - White Becomes President 17, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Wi, 1952 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Wi, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Wi-n, 1954-1955 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Wi-n, 1955-1956 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Wi-n, 1956-1957 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Wi-n, 1957-1959 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Wi-n, 1959-1960 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Wo, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Wo, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Wo-x, 1956-1957 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Wo-z, 1955-1956 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Wo-z, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Wo-z, 1958-1959 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Wo-z, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Wo-x-y-z, 1954-1955 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Wy, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Wy, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Wy-z, 1956-1957 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - X-y, 1955-1956 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Y, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Y, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Y, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Y, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Y, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Y, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Y, 1962-1963 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Y, 1963-1964 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Y, 1965-1966 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Y-z, 1954-1955 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - X-y, 1956-1957 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - X-y, 1957-1958 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - X-y, 1958-1959 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - X, Y, Z, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - XYZ, 1950 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - XYZ, 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - XYZ, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Z, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Z, 1952 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Z, 1953 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Z, 1955-1956 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Z, 1957-1958 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Z, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Z, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Z, 1964-1965 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - August, 1960 August (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - September, 1960 September (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - December-Houston, 1960 December 7 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - January, 1960-1961 January (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - January-Alexandria, Louisiana, 1960-1961 January 10 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - February, 1960-1961 February (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - January, 1961-62 January (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - March, 1961 March (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - April, 1961 April (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - April-Oklahoma City, 1961 April 16-24 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - May, 1961 May (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - June, 1961 June (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - July, 1961 July (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - August, 1961 August (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - September, 1961 September (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - October, 1961 October (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - November, 1961 November (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - December, 1961 December (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - February, 1962 February (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - March, 1962 March (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - April, 1961-1962 April (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - May, 1962 May (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - June, 1962 June (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - July, 1962 July (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - August, 1962 August (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - September, 1961-1962 September (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - October, 1962 October (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - October 29, 1962 October 29 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - November 1, 1962 November (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - November 2, 1962 November (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - June, 1963 June (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - August, 1963 August (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - October, 1962-1963 October (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - February, 1963-1964 February (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - March, 1964 March (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - April, 1963-1965 April (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - May, 1964 May (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - July, 1964 July (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - August, 1964 August (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - September, 1964 September (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - October, 1964 October (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - November, 1963-1964 November (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - December, 1964 December (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - January-Engagements, 1964-1965 January (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - February, 1964-1965 February (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - March, 1964-1965 March (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - April, 1964-1965 April (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - May, 1965 May (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - June, 1965 June (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - September, 1965 September (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - October, 1965 October (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - November, 1965 November (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - December, 1965 December (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - January-Engagements, 1965-1966 January (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - February-Engagements, 1965-1966 February (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - March-Engagements, 1966 March (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - April-Engagements, 1965-1966 April (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - People, 1945-1973; 2
    - Alldredge, E.P., 1945-1947, undated (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, Maurice, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Dr. Maurice J. (Hong Kong Baptist College), 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Armstrong, A.J., 1951-1953 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Armstrong, Dr. and Mrs. A. J., 1954-1955 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. A.J. (Mary), 1955-1956 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. A.J. (Mary), 1957-1958 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. A.J. (Mary), 1958-1959, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. A.J. (Mary), 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Avery, J.B., 1960 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Baker, Paul, 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Baker, Paul, 1956-1957 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Baker, Paul, 1956-1958 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Baker, Paul, 1958-1959 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Baker, W.G., 1952 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Baker, W.G., 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Baker, W.G., 1954-1956 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Baker, W.G., 1956-1957 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Baker, W.G., 1957-1958 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Baker, W.G., 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Baker, W.G., 1960-1964 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Belew, George, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Biddle, (Major General) William, undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Bridgers, John, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Brown, Bert P., 1972 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Bruner, J.W., 1948-1950 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Bryan, Judge Alva, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Bryant, C.E., 1952 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Bryant, C.E., 1953 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Bryant, C.E., 1953-1956 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Bryant, C.E., 1956-1957 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Butler, Ira, 1948-1950 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Butt, H.E., 1950 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Butt, Howard, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Butt, Howard, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Howard, 1954-1956 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Howard E., 1957 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Butt, Howard E. Jr., 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Butt, Howard E. Jr., 1962-1963 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Caldwell, C.M., 1949-1951 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Commack, Pauline, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Canon, Mrs. Val H., 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Capp, Glenn R., 1954-1956 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Capp, Glenn R., 1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Capp, Glenn R., 1957-1958 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Capp, Glenn R., 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Capp, Glenn R., 1960 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Carpenter, J. Walter, 1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Carroll, T.D., 1953 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Carroll, T.D., 1951-1952 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Carroll, T.D., 1954-1956 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Carroll, T.D., 1957-1958 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Carson, M.F. (Nightwatchman), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Carson, M..F., 1951-1952 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Cartlidge, Jared I., 1949 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Chu, David, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Chu, David, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Chu, David, 1954-1955 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Chunn, Prentis W. Jr., 1951 (Box 105, Folder 28)